How are you doing?
How are you?
I want to see your comments when it starts.
Oh, but, oh, they're here.
Oh! Yoo-hoo!
Thank you very much, thank you all. Thanks to all of you who are waiting.
And to those of you who are opening the door, thank you very much.
I'm Kaho Kobayashi.
Yoo-hoo!
What's this all about?
Is there any slack in it? I'm sure you're all getting a little nervous,
I'm not going to tell you yet. I'm not going to tell you yet.
Oh, is it important or not? Yes, it is.
You can still watch the streaming of the play I performed in January called "An Important Story",
I hope you will check it out, too, but that's not it.
But that's not it.
I'm going to talk about something else today.
Yesterday, I was in Fukuoka Park for the spring tour.
I came back today.
I had Thai chazuke for the first time.
I ordered sesame kanpachi.
I had sesame kanpachi chazuke.
I had it with Maya and Riko.
It was delicious! It was my first time to eat it!
I was thinking, "Wow, it shows the best of the Japanese people!
That's right.
What? I wasn't lying on the floor.
That's the wall.
Hey, it's not that popular stuff.
Yes, it was delicious. Sesame kanpachi.
It was delicious.
You can eat it now.
You can eat fish.
It didn't smell fishy at all.
It's more like...
It's just the kind of thing you'd expect from a first meal.
And the broth was really good, too.
Well...
What have you been doing?
Already the second day of Golden Week?
I'm back.
What do you think? I wonder how long they'll say that.
I wonder how long they'll keep talking about the salmon incident.
I wonder how long they'll keep digging up my black history.
I can eat a little more.
But I'm not ready for sea urchin and salmon roe.
I see.
What do you think?
Oh, yes, the EbiChu Cafe. What do you think? What do you think?
Are you having fun?
Did you go?
We went one step ahead of you.
We had a chance to try some of the food.
I haven't posted the pictures yet.
I'll give you a picture of it when it's ready.
Yes, I'm kind of a Mille Crepe
I ate my own Mille Crepe and also Maya's menu.
I also ate Maya's menu.
It was so delicious!
It was soooo delicious!
Oh, it's so cute, isn't it?
The goods were so cute this time!
That tumbler? I thought, "I want a tumbler.
That's right.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes, Mayu's one is chicken.
Chicken number.
It was delicious.
Oh, you bought the poster? Thank you.
I'm glad.
What do you think?
Oh, yeah. What was the chilled Chinese noodles yesterday? Oh, well, um...
I found some chilled chuka at a convenience store.
I feel like eating it when I find it at the convenience store.
Yes, I had it yesterday morning.
I started it yesterday morning.
Yes, it's totally Fukuoka related.
It's not "To-Chukka", but "To-Chukka" you can buy anywhere.
Okay, then...
Do you have any questions?Say, "Do you have any questions?" "Do you have any questions?
Of course you do. What are you going to talk about?
That's all I'm going to say.
That's right.
Oh, great.
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
Earrings, earrings, these are... ear cuffs?
What do you call them, ear cuffs?
Something to hold them in? Pinch?
It's a pinch.
Oh.
Hey, what is it? What's this for? Well, that's, uh, that's, uh, that's right.
I'll tell you in about 40 minutes,
I'll tell you exactly what it is.
Happy news?
What do you think?
I don't know.
Thank you for saying I look good with the short cut.
But it's been about 3 years since I had a short cut.
I haven't had a short cut in about three years, and I'm a little slow on the uptake.
I've forgotten.
I think it's better to go every month, right?
I should go get it done soon.
Thank you. I really like short hair.
I really like it.
I'm getting on a plane at 6:00 p.m.
What should I do? What should I do?
I'll tell you around 6:05 p.m.?
I just can't see it. I just can't see it.
I can't see it, I can't see it, I can't see it.
Once we're at...
I've got 2,390 people watching me.
Thank you!
Mishin
What should I do?
What the...
How about...
Do you have any? A question.
Nothing?
Nothing? That's...
That's sad.
Okay, I'll just say it.
Oh, uh..,
450, 2,450 more.
So, should we say it now?
Let's just say it, huh?
I'm so happy to announce...
I, Hanaho Kobayashi, am releasing a photo book!
That's great!
I'm so happy! Yo! Yo!
Yes! Yes, yes! Well, here and there, there were a lot of comments that I wish it was a classic, or a photo book, or a drama, or something like this, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy. But, but what a surprise! It's my wish.
The title is "Me! It will be a photo book called "Me! I'll also tell you the release date. The release date is June 12! It's my birthday!
Happy birthday!
Okay, so let's get started.
Hey, Min-chan!
Shall we take a look? Okay? Okay, first of all...
First of all, I'm surprised.
There are two covers.
Wow! So I'll show you the regular version first.
Well, here it is!
It's kind of white.
The one in the white costume, smiling happily...
That's the normal version. And this is...
And this one...
And here's the other one with a full face on the cover.
The other one has a full face on the cover.
And here's the other one that I'm interested in, the one with the full face.
She's a genius who can take really cute pictures of girls.
She's so cute!
And the make-up artist and the costume artist who are the stars of the moment...
It's true... we were able to use all the professional help we could get.
We were able to use the magic of the professionals to our advantage, and we were able to take this picture.
There are so many things I want to say, so I'll go through them in order.
First of all...
This is the standard edition, and the other one is a Rakuten Books exclusive.
The other one is available only at Rakuten Books.
I want you to get both of them.
But this one from Rakuten Books is a limited edition.
It's a little bit different from the other one.So I'm a little different from the usual Hanaho Kobayashi.
And I'm a little too nervous about it.
If you can't watch it, you can also watch the regular version together with it.
It's just the same as always, just the same as always.
If you want to get your heart pounding, you know what I mean?
I hope you'll get the Rakuten Books limited edition, too.
In short, I'd like you to get both of them.
This is the signed edition.
This is where the signed copies are sold.
The one with the autograph on the regular edition is
The one with the autograph on the regular edition is only for Black Tiger.
You can buy it at the place that sells a lot of Maebilis goods and so on.
You can buy it there.
And the one with the signature on the limited edition is
Rakuten Books, Inc.
If you want this autographed copy
The pre-order starts tomorrow, May 1st, Monday at 12:00 noon.
The reservation period is until 23:59 on May 16th.
You can reserve until 23:59 on May 16th.
If you want the autograph, please make your reservation from 12:00 noon tomorrow.
If you want to get the autograph, please make your reservation as soon as possible.
If you want to get it signed, please make your reservation as soon as possible from 12:00 pm tomorrow.
And a new species!
Ladies and gentlemen!
We are going to have an event!
First of all, I would like to give them to you after my birthday solo live on June 12, after my birthday solo live Poland 8.
I think it may be difficult for those who have Cinderella time to attend the event because of the limited time after the live.
I'm happy to announce that there will be an event at the bookstore on July 2nd.
I'd like to hand this out to all of you, and I'd like to say that it's very kind of you.
The event will be held at a bookstore on July 2nd, and the venue is hmv & books Shibuya.
If you buy one book, I will give it to you, but if you buy two books, you will get to take two shots with me.
If you buy two copies, you will get two shots with me.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a photo with me.
I'd like to present you with a new kind of photo that only I'm in, so please join us!
We're looking forward to seeing you. What do you think, everyone?
What do you think? I'm so happy. I'm so happy we can be happy together.
So, Poland...
If you're coming to Poland, I'd like to give it to you as it is.
It's Cinderella time! I'll see you on July 2nd.
I'm looking forward to seeing you there, too.
We're looking forward to seeing you there as well. The reservation for this event itself will be open from Monday, May 8th at 8:00 p.m.
There are so many things to do, I'm sure you're all wondering what to do, what to do, what to do, what to do, what to do, what to do, what to do, what to do, what to do, what to do...
I'd like to receive a signed copy, but I'd also like to receive a signed copy, so you'll have to ask yourself what you want to do.
If you purchase at hmv & books online and hmv store loppies, you will get a photo of yourself.
There are 5 kinds of photos in total, and one of them is included at random.
Like this
Like this...
You'll get one of these, right?
It was really hard to choose one.
I couldn't decide, I couldn't decide, I couldn't decide.
So, since it comes with one photo, I'm sure you'll be able to choose the one you like best.
Anyway...
Anyway, I'd really appreciate it if you could help me with that.
For more details, please check out our website.
I might post it on Stories.
I'd be happy if you could take a look at our website.
What do you think?
Oh...
Look at this.
If you know what I mean.
Huh?
Hair.
Huh? Like that.
It's shorter here.
But over here...
Huh? It's like...
Longer? It's like...
What's going on?
I'm just saying, you know, if you could just see what's inside.
I'm sure you'll see what I mean.
I'm glad. Everyone's happy.
Yes, yes, the cover.
Yes, yes.
Yes, yes, you guessed it.
It's the same inside.
The cover, if I'm misleading you right now...
The cover is different.
The inside is the same.
That's right.That's right.
Short or long, it's practically free now.
That's great. Thank you very much.
It's free.
Oh, what do you think? Can I see both? You'll have to wait and see.
I'm just saying.
I'll buy two copies just to make sure.
Thank you very much.
I'd be happy if you came to see me. I heard it's expensive.
I'm curious.
Let me tell you the price. The price is...
Two Hideo Noguchi and a 500 yen coin.
That's 2,500 yen.
How about 2,500 yen?
Of course, I don't know if it's a price you can afford.
Everyone has a different sense of value.
But I think it's a great deal.
It's a lot of things.
I'm sure you'll be very pleased with what we have to offer.
I think it's great that each of the sister teams has their own photo book.
I've always admired their photo books, and I'd like to see mine in that lineup.
I'd love to have mine in that lineup.
I wanted to do this and that, and with the help of all the professionals, I was able to create this piece.
I'm really happy about it.
That's right.
By all means.
Yes, I'm very happy.
Which publisher?
Thank you.
SDP.
Thank you very much.
Thank you. Thank you.
It's nice to hear that. - Yes, it is. - Yes, it is.
I see. I'm not the type to be self-confident.
I'm not the type to have self-confidence.
I've always had this feeling that I'm going to be beautiful when I grow up.
I'm going to be beautiful, so I'll be okay.
I've always felt that the best time for me as a human being is around 22 years old.
I think the best time for me as a human being is around the age of 22, and I still have a little bit of adultery in me.
But I'm becoming more and more mature.
I think that I'm still in the green stage of maturity as an idol, and as a human being.
And also as a human being, or as a woman, or as a human being.
I think that I was able to make it happen at a very good time.
I really want to tell my grandchildren... that this is my grandmother when she was young.
I'd like to do that. I see.
Anyway, I'm really happy if you all could welcome me like this.
I'd be really happy if you all could welcome me. That's what I was delivering today.
How was it? Surprised? How was it?
Did you like it? I often tell my grandchildren... at their birthdays...
Yes, I'm looking forward to my old age.
That's why I'm so happy that I was able to preserve this, you know, this form of my youth.
Yes, I am.
I'm so happy! Thank you all for being so happy.
I'm so glad I made it on time to the plane.
That's great.
I'm so glad. I almost missed the most important part of the show because I didn't give it enough time.
The photographer, you know, it wasn't Mariko.
It was taken by a photographer named Ayako.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
How old are you now?
I'm 22.
I'm 24.
Oh!
Mmm-hmm.
Don't say "mature".
I will say "mature.
You're going to mature as a human being.
That's right.
Water's edge? Look at Cocona's.
She's cute, but you know, I'm not in charge of her.
That's right.
I'd like to go for our first two-shot.
That would make me happy. I'd love to take a good picture with you.
But I'm glad. I was expecting that. Really? Really? -Thank you.
I'd like to do kotei, too. -That's right.
We have a lot of sexy people too.
I'm not in charge of sexy.
You're in charge of grandma.Grandma's in charge.
I'm glad. I'll have to buy a lot of pictures for Po's logo.
I'll have to buy a lot of pictures of Poe's logo.
It's just a small contribution to my enjoyment of the logo. Thank you.
Thank you.
Yes, it is.
Thank you very much.
I don't know.
Well, something like that.
I've already told you what I wanted to tell you.
But let's go over it one last time. Reservations
First of all, if you're interested in getting a signed copy...
Tomorrow, Monday, May 1st, at 12:00 noon.
We'll start taking reservations at 12:00 noon on Monday, May 1st.
And it will be open until 23:59 on the 16th.
Please take a look at it!
And for those of you who would like to participate in the event...
May 8th at 8:00pm.
Please consider making a reservation for this event as well!
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it, too.
I'll make a reservation tomorrow.
It says "photo book" on it.
I'm glad you made it in time.
That's right.
What are you going to do? Well, goodbye at 6:00 p.m.?
Maybe I'll take a break.
Screentime. Screentime, please.
Just 10 seconds of screentime?
You mean, while you're holding this?
Okay, well, since we're here, I'd like you all to help me with the promotion.
I'd like you all to help me with this promotional activity.
Wait a minute.
Yes, this is it.
Okay, I'll give you 10 seconds.
It's time to take a picture!
I'm not going to let you take a picture.
I'm sorry I moved it... but you'll have to use your advanced technology to hold it back.
Okay, screw time is over.
It's good. No, it's really good, really good.
I don't know if I should say this, but...
Of course, if I had a professional photographer take pictures of me...
I mean, you know, it's like...
I mean, there are so many photos that I want to use, you know.
It was really hard to choose the one I wanted to use.
I had a hard time choosing the one I wanted to use.
We talked about it and had a meeting to make it.
Yes, I really want you to wait for it.
Oh, yes, the backbeat is also very nice.
I'll show you the backbeat another time! That's what I mean.
That's how it is, isn't it?
Oh, did I cut it off by mistake?
Don't cut it?
Oh, really?
What? Who's that woman in the back? Who's that woman in the back?
Stop it!
I won't shoot in the green back.
What are you talking about?
What are you talking about? What are you talking about?
Uh-oh.
Oh, do you have a hashtag for publicity? We'll think of one together.
What should we do? We'll think of a hashtag together.
What would be a good hashtag?
Photo album of Kou-chan... That's safe.
I wonder if there's anything...
I see...
I turned off the screen by mistake when I took the picture.
Sorry!
I'm sorry.
Thank you for opening it up again.
Thank you.
Oh.
Let's see...
Uh...
Not much.
I know, right?
Since the title is me
Me.Me.
I just thought it was me, didn't I?
Who or what is this? I was like, "Who's this?
Poe. Poe's photo album.
And there, too. It's safe.
It's easy to see.
It's a photo album, right?
What would you like?
Kobayashi, I...
I'm not sure.
I don't know...
I don't know, but I'm starting to see a scrubbing brush in my head.
I don't like that hashtag.
You know what I'm thinking...
I don't know... it's not so much the edginess of it... it's more like...
It's not so much the edge, to be honest...
Not too many pictures of you, me, Ali's mom...
It's a little...
You know, Ali's mom...
I don't know if it's a hashtag.
That's right... Hanaho Kobayashi's photo book, right?
My photo album is me, I'm Po-Po, I'm my Hanaho, my tawashi.
Shall I wash it?
Shall I wash it? What would you like?
I am Hanaho Kobayashi.
Oh!
I want Kaho Kobayashi.
Straight out of Kobayashi's photo album.
That's true. It's nice.
What do you think? I'm a little indecisive.
That's the thing.
Logo. Photo book for logo.
I like it.
Oh, wait a minute, when I decide on a hashtag...
I'll say goodbye, this distribution
I want my grandchildren to see me
Thanks, but it's too soon
It's too soon for a hashtag
I want to say it when they're older.
I'm not that grandson yet.
I want to show it to all of you.
I'm thinking long term.
I'll see what I can do.
Grandma, it's me.
I'm thinking of a fisherman's dumpling stand.
You're messing with me. You're messing with me.
You're messing with me.
Poland Poland Photo Album
I don't want you to think that this is some kind of photo album of Poland, because it really is that country.
I think Poland is a bit of a cacker... portfolio
Oh!
I'm Kaho Kobayashi
What? Is that a lot?
What do you like?
I'm Kaho Kobayashi.
I heard that Hanaho Kobayashi is going to publish a photo book.
That's kind of nice.
That's possible.
A photo book.
Ha ha.
But I'd like something catchy.
I don't know.
A little bit seriously really indecisive
I'm a little...
Fairies!
Would you please choose the fairies with me?
Fairies, me, me, Hanaho Kobayashi's first photo book.
You must be Irie, Kaho Kobayashi.
Certainly.
Let's try that one.
The top one probably has my name on it, so it's much easier to name.
I see, two or one is better?
How about my first photo book, Kaho Kobayashi?
I'll go with that one.
I've asked the fairies to pick out a good catch for me.
Okay, thank you all very much!
I'm going to use the hashtag, "My first photo book of Kaho Kobayashi.
I'm thinking of making it a hashtag that says, "My first photo book, Hanaho Kobayashi.
It was a quick decision, you know, you're a fairy with good judgment, aren't you?It was an instant decision. You know, I knew you were a judgmental fairy.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, you're a very judgmental fairy.
You know, in a situation like this...
I should tell you what to do.
I'll say it again.
Hashtag
I, Kaho Kobayashi's first photo book
Please use the hashtag "I'm Kaho Kobayashi's first photo book.
Hashtags are easy to understand.
Is it okay if I use hiragana?
Please use hiragana.
I'll write in hiragana and Hanao Kobayashi in kanji.
It's my first photo book.
All in kanji.
Is that okay then?
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Well then...
I guess it's time to say goodbye.
Thank you.
I don't know how you're spending your time.
Some of you are working, or at the office.
I don't know.
I really, uh...
Thank you for watching.
Well then...
I'm done.
See you later.
Thank you very much.
I'd be happy if you could wait until my birthday.
That's all for now, this is Kanon Kobayashi.
Bye bye!